All right, you're done. Let's go look at the
好的， 你做完了这些。我们来看看
solution. Where we left off last time as you can
结果。当我们上次退出的时候我们有
see we have two empty queries for LOCATION_ID and
两个空白的查询， 分别是LOCATION_ID和
LOCATION. These two queries look a lot like the queries
LOCATION。 这两个查询跟我们之前做的
we have for weather. For LOCATION_ID this looks almost
关于天气的查询很像.  特别是 LOCATION_ID这个查询简直
exactly like what we do for weather. Except we use
跟我们做的天气的查询一样。 除了我们使用了一个
a hard coded query, rather than relying on the one
硬编码的默认查询, 而不是在函数中带入一
passed into the function. Since we know that this is
参数。既然我们知道这个参数
always going to be a long integer value, it is
一直是一个长整型的数值， 这就让我们创建
easy to just build the value into the query string. Location,
这个查询的字符串变的比较容易了。
on the other hand, looks almost exactly like the weather
所以从另外一方面看， 这个查询就和天气的那个非常相似了
query. We just pass all the parameters into the database. You
我们仅仅需要把所有的参数都放进数据库。 你
didn't think you're going to get away without testing, did you?
该不会是想在没有任何测试之前就闪人吧？
Don't worry, it's really easy to add this test. It turns
别担心， 这个测试非常容易添加。只
out that calling our function within the provider, works almost
需要在 provider 里面调用我们的函数，这个几乎
exactly the same as the way we did the weather table.
跟我们之前调用那个天气的表格的方法一样呀。
All we have to do is replace WeatherEntry.CONTENT_URI with
我们仅仅需要做一个小变化，把WeatherEntry.CONTENT_URI 和
LocationEntry.CONTENT_URI. And of course we still have to delete the
LocationEntry.CONTENT_URI 互换。 当然我们还是需要删除
two columns that we can't support. Now that will actually
两列我们不能支出的表格。 现在这个就能完完全全
work. So, let's test that to make sure that works.
工作了。让我测试一下啊。
And our test passed, as expected. The interesting thing about
一如既往的，我们测试通过了。 有趣事是
this test is that it's just only testing the first
这些测试只是检测了第一个
query and it just happens to work because we deleted
查询同时它能够通过测试是因为我们在测试之前删除了那个
the database before the start. It'd be much more interesting
数据库。查询这个行是非常有趣的，
to query for the row that we just inserted. And this will test the
因为它会同时测试其他的
other query. Now, let's run the test again. And those also passed. So, we have
查询呢。 现在，让我们再次来检测一下。 发现了什么？ 全部通过啦。 所以呢，
some of our queries from our content
这些查询其中的一些是从provider的功能里
provider functioning. But, unfortunately, we still have
附带的。 但是， 我们依然需要做
to do some of the more complicated
一些更复杂的事情
things in the provider. Let's talk about joins.
这些复杂的事就是 joins